Northman 1: Oi!
Northman 1：喂！
Northman 2: Mind out.
Northman 2：当心。
Move!
动!
Northman: Look, on the west wall!
Northman：看，在西墙上！
Soldier 1: Get down to the crypt!
士兵1：到地下室去！
Soldier 2: Just hold.
士兵2：稍等。
Man: We'll take him.
男：我们带他去。
Lady mormont: Come on, help the lads!
莫尔蒙夫人：快来，帮帮这些小伙子！
Soldier 3: Yes, my lady.
士兵3：是的，夫人。
Lady mormont: Quickly, now! Quickly!
Get those in position.
莫尔蒙夫人：快，现在！很快!
把那些放好。
Soldier 3: Come on.
Soldier 4: Close the gate!
士兵3：来吧。
士兵4：把门关上！
Soldier 5: That's it.
士兵5：就是这样。
Oh, for fuck's sake.
You took your time.
哦，看在上帝的份上。
你慢慢来。
Do you speak their tongue?
你会说他们的语言吗？
Tell them to lift their swords.
叫他们举起剑来。
Valar morghulis.
Valar morghulis。
Valar dohaeris.
Valar dohaeris。
Open the gate!
打开大门！
Soldier 1: Open the gate!
士兵1：打开大门！
Soldier 2: Open the gate!
士兵2：打开大门！
Man: Come. Come on.
男:来了。来吧。
Easy.
容易实现。
There's no need to execute me,
ser davos.
没必要处决我
ser达沃斯。
I'll be dead before the dawn.
黎明前我就会死去。
Cease fire!
停止射击!
The night king is coming.
夜王来了。
The dead are already here.
死者已经在这里了。
Stand your ground!
坚守阵地！
Arya: Get down to the crypt.
艾莉亚：到地下室去。
Sansa: I'm not abandoning my people.
珊莎：我不会抛弃我的人民。
Arya: Take this and go.
艾莉亚：拿着这个走吧。
I don't know how to use it.
我不知道怎么用。
Stick them with the pointy end.
用尖的一端粘住它们。
Samwell: Edd!
Samwell: Edd !
Dolorous edd: Sam, get up!
忧伤的艾迪：山姆，起来！
Oh, god. Sam.
哦,上帝。山姆。
Fall back! Fall back!
撤退!撤退!
Fall back!
撤退!
Soldier: Come on!
士兵：加油！
Open the gate!
打开大门！
Soldier 1: Open the gate!
士兵1：打开大门！
Soldier 2: Let us in!
士兵2：让我们进去！
Soldier 1: Open the gate!
士兵1：打开大门！
Soldier 3: Open the gate!
士兵3：打开大门！
Soldier 4: Keep moving!
士兵4：继续前进！
Soldier 5: Come on!
士兵5：加油！
Lady mormont: Keep moving, fast.
Soldier 5: To your posts.
莫尔蒙夫人：继续走，快点。
士兵5：各就各位。
Soldier 6: Go!
Soldier 7: Keep moving!
士兵6：走！
士兵7：继续前进！
Soldier 1: Come on, run!
士兵1：快跑！
Soldier 8: Keep moving!
士兵8：继续前进！
Protect the retreat!
保护撤退！
Stand your ground!
坚守阵地！
Dany!
丹妮!
Soldier 1: Grab your weapon now!
士兵1：拿起你的武器！
Soldier 2: Guard the barricades!
士兵2：守住路障！
Soldier 3: Through that pass!
士兵3：穿过那个隘口！
Brienne: Hey! Hey! Hey!
一起:嘿!嘿!嘿!
Soldier 4: Close up the gaps!
士兵4：堵住缺口！
Go! Hey! Go! Go!
走吧!嘿!走吧!走吧!
Get in! Get in!
进入!进入!
Get in! Come on!
进入!来吧!
Soldier 1: Move!
士兵1：快走！
Retreat!
撤退!
- Come on!
-拜托！
Lady mormont: Protect the gate!
莫尔蒙夫人：守住城门！
Soldier 1: Protect the gate!
士兵1：守住大门！
They're coming! Come on!
他们来了!来吧!
Fall back!
撤退!
Light the trench!
点亮战壕！
Soldier 2: Wait!
Soldier 3: Light the trench!
士兵2：等等！
士兵3：点亮战壕！
She can't see us.
她看不见我们。
Light the trenches!
点亮战壕！
Soldier 1: With a torch,
light the trenches!
士兵1：拿着火把，
点亮战壕！
- Right there.
- Soldier 2: Torch it!
-就在那儿。
-士兵2：烧了它！
Light the trenches!
点亮战壕！
Clegane.
Clegane。
Woman:
You must try not to worry yourself.
女士:
你必须尽量不要为自己担心。
At least we're already in a crypt.
至少我们已经在地窖里了。
If we were up there,
如果我们在上面
we might see something
everyone else is missing.
我们可能会看到一些东西
其他人都不见了。
Something that makes a difference.
能带来改变的东西。
What?
怎么啦？
Remember the battle of Blackwater?
I brought us through the mud gate.
还记得黑水之战吗？
我带我们穿过泥门。
- And got your face cut in half.
- And it made a difference.
-你的脸被切成两半。
-结果很不一样。
If I was out there right now...
如果我现在在外面…
You'd die.
你会死。
There's nothing you can do.
你什么也做不了。
You might be surprised
at the lengths I'd go
你可能会感到惊讶
我所做的一切
to avoid joining
the army of the dead.
为了避免加入
死亡之军。
I could think of no organization
less suited to my talents.
我想不出任何组织
不太适合我的才能。
Witty remarks
won't make a difference.
诙谐的评论
不会有什么不同。
That's why we're down here,
none of us can do anything.
这就是我们来这里的原因
我们谁也做不了什么。
It's the truth.
这是事实。
It's the most heroic thing
we can do now...
这是最英勇的事情
我们现在可以做……
Look the truth in the face.
面对现实吧。
Maybe we should have stayed married.
也许我们应该保持婚姻关系。
You were the best of them.
你是他们中最好的。
What a terrifying thought.
多么可怕的想法。
It wouldn't work between us.
我们之间不会有结果的。
Why not?
为什么不呢?
The dragon queen.
龙后。
Your divided loyalties
would become a problem.
你分裂的忠诚
会成为一个问题。
Missandei: Yes.
Missandei:是的。
Without the dragon queen,
there'd be no problem at all.
没有龙后
完全没有问题。
We'd all be dead already.
我们早就死了。
They lit the trench.
他们点燃了战壕。
Bran...
糠……
I just want you to know...
我只是想让你知道…
I wish...
我希望……
The things I did...
我做的那些事…
Everything you did
brought you where you are now.
你所做的一切
把你带到现在的位置。
Where you belong.
属于你的地方。
Home.
首页。
I'm going to go now.
我现在要走了。
Go where?
去哪里?
Man the walls!
守卫城墙！
Soldier 1: Man the walls!
士兵1：守住城墙！
Man the wall!
守住墙！
Man the walls!
守卫城墙！
Come on!
来吧!
Get out there! Get moving!
出去！行动起来!
Come on. Come on! Come on!
来吧。来吧!来吧!
Go, go, go!
快，快，快！
Come on!
来吧!
Soldier 1: They're against the wall!
士兵1：他们靠墙了！
Get more men up here!
派更多的人上来！
- Fill the gaps, quickly!
- Get in there!
-填补空白，快！
-快进去！
Soldier 2: They're climbing the walls!
士兵2：他们在爬墙！
- Relieve the archers!
- Soldier 2: Relieve the archers!
-解除弓箭手！
-士兵2：解除弓箭手！
Archers on top!
弓箭手在上面！
Soldier 1: Move up!
Soldier 2: Go, go! Come here!
士兵1：往前走！
士兵2：快，快！来这里!
- Come on!
- Soldier 3: Move back!
-拜托！
士兵3：后退！
- Soldier 4: Stand away!
- Go on, go on. Go! Go.
士兵4：走开！
-继续，继续。走吧!走了。
Soldier 3: Step back.
Soldier 4: All the way, archers!
士兵3：退后。
士兵4：加油，弓箭手们！
Soldier 1: Hold the wall!
士兵1：守住墙！
Soldier 2: The wall,
they're coming up!
士兵2：墙，
他们上来了！
Soldier 3: Hold the wall!
Soldier 4: Hold the wall!
士兵3：守住墙！
士兵4：守住墙！
Draw!
画!
Come on!
来吧!
Soldier: They're coming up!
士兵：他们来了！
Look out!
当心!
Clegane!
Clegane !
Beric: Clegane!
Beric: Clegane !
Clegane, we need you!
克里冈，我们需要你！
You can't give up on us.
你不能放弃我们。
Fuck off! We can't beat them.
滚蛋!我们打败不了他们。
Don't you see that, you stupid whore?
你看不出来吗，你这个蠢婊子？
We're fighting death!
我们在与死神抗争！
They can't beat death.
他们无法战胜死亡。
Tell her that.
告诉她。
Ahhh!
啊!
Soldier 1: Open the door!
士兵1：开门！
Soldier 2: Open the door!
士兵2：开门！
Soldier 3: Come on!
Soldier 4: Open the door!
士兵3：加油！
士兵4：开门！
Open the door!
开门！
Soldier 4: Please!
士兵4：求你了！
Open it!
打开它!
Hound: Come on! Go!
猎狗：来吧！走吧!
- Come on!
- Beric: Run!
-拜托！
快跑！
Hound: We've gotta go!
猎狗：我们得走了！
Melisandre: The lord brought him back
for a purpose.
梅丽珊卓：上帝把他带回来了
为了一个目的。
Now that purpose has been served.
现在这个目的已经实现了。
I know you.
我了解你。
And I know you.
我也了解你。
You said we'd meet again.
你说过我们会再见面的。
And here we are.
现在我们到了。
At the end of the world.
在世界的尽头。
You said I'd shut many eyes forever.
你说我会永远闭上许多人的眼睛。
You were right about that too.
这一点你也说对了。
Brown eyes...
棕色的眼睛……
Green eyes...
绿色的眼睛……
And blue eyes.
还有蓝眼睛。
What do we say to the god of death?
我们该对死神说什么？
Not today.
不是今天。
Here they come!
他们来了！
Steady, lads.
稳定,小伙子。
Steady now.
稳定了。
Make every shot count.
让每一枪都有价值。
Man 1: Over there!
男1：在那边！
Man 2: There!
男2：看！
Get off.
下车。
Dracarys.
Dracarys。
Come on! Come on!
来吧!来吧!
No! No, no, no!
不!不，不，不！
- Bran!
- Go!
-麸!
——走吧!
Daenerys: Jorah!
Daenerys: Jorah !
Bran: Theon.
麸:全心全意地。
You're a good man.
你是个好人。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
I'm hurt.
我伤害了。